ACWA Hyman Blumberg Records 6015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Clippings. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Clippings. General., 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Numerous News Clippings. General., 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Language: English;Yiddish.
- Certificate. Hyman Blumberg, Advisor to Labor Delegation., 1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Certificate. Hyman Blumberg, Advisor to Labor Delegation., 1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)